live like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
world to keep brother
tanel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou not
make it to thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the Earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for why the Lord thy God
am a jealous God visiting the iniquities
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me and showing Mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him guils that take
up his name in vain remember the Sabbath
day to keep it holy six days sh thy
labor and do all thy work but the
seventh day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God in it thou shall not do any work
thou nor thy son nor thy daughter thy
man servant nor thy maid servant nor thy
cattle nor th stranger that is within
thy gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and rested the seventh day well
for the Lord bless the Sabbath day and
holiday honor thy father and thy mother
that thy days may be long long upon the
land which the Lord thy God give thee
thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou sh not be false witness against thy
neighbor thou not cover thy neighbor's
house thou not cover thy neighbor's wife
knowest man's servant noest ma servant
nor his Ox nor his ass nor anything that
is thy neighbors you read Exodus 21
through1 17 and may the Lord have a
blessing to the reading of his words in
Jesus name we pray amen amen
so here on question and answer you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible and if
we cannot find the answer we will seek
further counsel to bring you an answer
at a later time keep in mind that all
vague questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or a CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please for time's sake
be as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream and
you may begin to send in your questions
at this time even questions that pertain
to everlasting life we're just asking
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
to you the family that's on the panel
this evening we got brother Julius good
evening
everybody brother Dre good evening
brother Jerome Jon peace Brother tanzel
good evening sister
Deborah good
evening brother
Shawn good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
so sister Deborah let us begin with our
first
question okay uh there are several held
over questions though that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's
Q&A how
as in Acts 7: 55 and
56 did Stefan actually see Jesus
standing on the right hand of the father
or was this a vision of the future based
on Psalms 110 verse1 or had the father
already made Jesus enemies his foottoo
after Jesus
resurrected all right brother Julius how
will you shed some light on that
question there let's go to uh acts seven
stepan is rehearsing Israel history down
to the people pick it up at 7 and 51
let's see if it's a vision of what what
the book say actually is Act 7 brother
tzel 7 and 51 go ahead
ye stick stick stick stick NE and I'm
circumcising heart and ears you always
resist the Holy Ghost that's your
fathers did and so do ye verse 53
53 who have received the law by the
disposition of angels and have not kept
it and when they heard these things they
were cut to the heart and they on him
with their de so this is a actual
physical uh rejection of the total word
of God and they nashed on him with their
teeth go ahead but he being full of the
Holy Ghost looked up steadfastly into
heaven and saw the glory of God and saw
what the glory of God he saw this it
didn't say it was a vision he actually
saw this go ahead and Jesus standing on
the right hand of God and he recognized
Jesus because he was also an apostle
that replaced uh one of the Apostles but
continue and said behold I see the
heavens open and no I see a
vision the heavens open he said I see
the heavens on this is not a vision he
actually sees this go ahead and the son
of man standing on the right hand of God
and so therefore it is not a vision he
actually saw this this they did a
physical act and then uh he actually saw
this and then what did they do after
that at 58 they cast him out of the city
and then they stoned him to death so he
actually saw this Vision now the other
part of your question Psalm 110 has
nothing to do with this Jesus the right
hand has always sit on on the right hand
of the father only time he got up when
he came down in the flesh went back
after he did his mission sat on the
right hand of the father now as for your
your last part of that question that the
father already made Jesus enemies his
foot stol the answer is no how do I know
let's go to 1 Corinthians the 15th
chapter
Jesus the father has not yet made Jesus
enemies his foot stol acts 15 and we
going 24 to 26 10 acts 15 I'm sorry 1
Corinthians 15 1 Corinthians
15 24- 26 when you get it brother go
ahead then cometh the end when he shall
have delivered up the kingdom to God
even the father when he shall that yet
future that is yet future CU Jesus must
Reign go ahead when he shall have put
down all rules and all authority and
power uhhuh for he must rain till he
have put all enemies under his feet
uhhuh The Last Enemy that shall be
destroyed is death and that is the grave
people are still dying people are still
being buried and so death is still here
and death is an enemy to us because we
were created to live forever so no this
is not happening yet we're waiting on
this is this to happen I hope that uh
that clears some things up brother tzel
um brother uh
Cornel all right thank you for that
brother and uh we're gonna move on to
our next
question yes brother Anthony horsey says
can you please share some light on Luke
7 verse 19 why out of all did John the
Baptist ask this and what is the
significance all right so it's two
questions inside of that one let's go to
Luke 7 Luke 7 because they want to know
why out of all this did John the Baptist
WID he ask this question and what was
the significance of it so let's go to
Luke
7 when you get there brother let's see
here let's pick it
up at that verse
18 I think Luke 7 and 18 go ahead
brother and The Disciples of John show
him all these things and John calling
unto him two of his disciples sent them
to Jesus saying are thou he that should
come or look weak for
another when the man all right so good
that's good so this was a two-part
question here um skip down brother and
let's see what Jesus said read verse 21
go
ahead and in that same hour he cured
many of their infirmities and plagues
and of evil spirits and and unto many
that were blind he gave sight
yeah then then Jesus answered and he
said unto them go your way and tell John
what things you have seen and heard how
that the blind see and the lame walk
leers are cleanse the deaf ha the dead I
raised
to the poor the gospel is preached uhhuh
and bless is he soever shall not be
offended in me all right and blessed is
he so Jesus had told the disciples that
John sent he said go back and tell them
that hey that the lame walk the lepers
are heal the blind see and that the poor
have the gospel preached unto them and
blessed is he whosoever shall not be
offended in me and no one on this panel
is offended in
Jesus so let's find out about why this
question was like let's go to Matthew 11
why John sent them Matthew the 11
chapter and let's see where where John
was
at because he wasn't able to witness it
for himself so he sent his disciples
there and say hey go out there and see
is he the
one Matthew 11 And1 go ahead brother and
it came to pass when Jesus had made an
end of commanding his 12 disciples he
departed departed then to teach him to
preach in their cities uhhuh now when
John had heard in the prison The Words
of Christ he sent two of his disciples
yes because John was in prison at this
time so he wasn't able to see it for
himself but he heard of all these great
works that was going on he wanted to say
hey is this the one go ahead and said
unto him are thou he that shall come or
do we look for another
and Jesus answered and said unto them go
and show John again those things which
you do hear and
see the blind receive their sight and
the lame walk the lepers are cleansed
and the deaf hear the dead are raised up
and the poor have the gospels preached
to them and blessed whosoever shall be
not offended in me we not offended at
all now let's turn over that John 1 and
let's see the reason what is the
significance of this because John knew
that he was the light but he knew it was
one that was going to come after him
even though he was not that light the
one that was coming at them is the light
John one and pick it up brother at that
verse
four go ahead in him was light and the
light was the light of men uhhuh the
light shineth in darkness and the
Darkness comprehended it not yeah there
was a man sent from God whose name was
John the same came for a witness to Bear
witness of the life that all men through
him might believe so John knew that the
one that was coming after him is the one
that was gonna come preaching teaching
healing doing all this thing go ahead he
was not that light but was sent to Bear
witness of that light and John was not
that light but he was sent to Bear
witness to say that there's one coming
after me verse 14 go ahead
and the Word was made flesh and dwelt
among us we beheld his glory the glory
as of the only begotten of the father
full of grace and truth this is the one
that was coming after John that John was
bearing witness of going before that
light verse 15 then we're gonna read one
more verse go ahead and John bear
witness of him and cried saying this was
he of whom I spake that he that he that
cometh after me is preferred before me
hether coming after me is preferred
before me so John knew that he was just
coming to give witness to the one that
was coming after him and what else did
he say about the one that was coming
after him verse 27 and that'll be
it he he it is who's coming after me is
preferred it before me whose shoes
latches I am not worthy to un loose so
this was Jesus that John was talking
about here and that's why he asked that
question because he was in prison saying
hey I'm hearing these great works go ask
us that him and then he was letting it
be known that hey he was not that light
but he was a forerunner for Jesus and
the one coming after him is the one that
created all things that was preferred
before him and that's all I
get and we hope that that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
sister yes moving on sister Israel asks
what scriptures can I show to my
classmates about astrology and
Witchcraft being wrong they heavily
believes in this and some have practiced
Buddhism this stuff is heavy even unto
this day but what you say
Dre yeah let's go to Deuteronomy the
18th chapter and we're going to pick it
up at verse uh 10 do the omy 18 and10
and we'll read till
12 go ahead when you get it
Tel there should not be found among you
anyone that maketh a son or daughter to
pass through the fire or that uses Devon
nature or an observer of times or an
enchanter or
witch or a charmer or a counselor with
familiar Spirit or a wizard or a
necromancer for all that do these things
are abomination unto the Lord and
because of these Abominations the Lord
thy God doth drive them out from before
thee these are Abominations to the Lord
and all them things that you talking
about is included in that let's over to
Exodus the 22nd
chapter Exodus 22 and we G to read Verse
18 Exodus 22 and8 go ahead brother when
you get
it that's I suffer Wich to live that's
good so
witches in the Kingdom going to get they
got killed I mean before when we were in
our laws witches
died they were killing so this wasn't
something that the Lord Smiled On Let's
go to Deuteronomy 4 and look at one more
thing Deuteronomy
4 and we going to pick it up at verse 13
Deuteronomy 4 and13 go ahead brother and
he declare unto you his coven which he
commanded you to perform even Ten
Commandments and he wrote them upon two
tables of
stone and the Lord commanded me at that
time to teach you statutes and judgments
that you might do them in the land
whether ye go over to possess it this is
what we should be doing the Commandments
but go ahead take you therefore good
heed unto yourselves for ye saw no man
of similitude on the day that the Lord
spake unto you in HB out of the midst of
the
fire unless you corrupt yourselves and
make you a grave in image the similitude
of any figure the likeness of male or
female SK down and read verse
19 and lest thou lift up thy eyes unto
heaven and when thou see is the sun and
the moon and the stars even all the
hosts of Heaven should us be driven to
worship them and to serve them which the
Lord thy God have divided into All
Nations under the whole Heaven God
didn't give us that to do he gave us his
Commandments that's what we should go by
I would say give them that I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
brother because we know that the land
that the lord gave us the people were
doing that before we even got there and
he say don't do like them right thank
you for that brother all right sister
Deborah we moving to our next one yes uh
June nor for asked in Mark 2:s
23-
28 especially in verse
27 does this mean the Sabbath was a
Commandment that was added after Jesus
made man and uh she states I know and
understand the Commandments were
enforced before man man was
made all right so um ter let's go to
that Mark 2 Mark 2 and let's pick it up
at that verse
23 and they want emphasis on 27 and the
guest caller would shed some light from
there read
[Music]
you so it is Mark 2: 23-
28 wa and it came to pass that he went
through the corn fields on the Sabbath
day and his disciples began as they went
to plug the ears of corn and the
Pharisees said unto him behold why do
they on the Sabbath day that which is
not lawful why do they do that on the
Sabbath day which is not lawful and he
said unto them but have ye never what
David did when he had need and was a
hunger and he that were with him and he
went into the house of God and the days
of abiathar the high priest and did eat
the showbread which is not lawful to eat
but for the priest and gave also to them
which were with him and he said unto
them the Sabbath was made for man and
not man for the Sabbath therefore the
son of man is Lord also of the Sabbath
okay the first thing is it says that the
Sabbath day made uh uh added to the
Commandments there is no uh uh scripture
that tell you that the Sabbath day was
added later on with the ten
commandments so the answer was that it
was no but for it when it say that the
27 that the Sabbath was made for man
that's because the Lord did give man one
day
to rest from all his labor now let's go
quickly to Exodus the 23rd
chapter and we're going to read verse 12
read it when you get
there six day shall thou do thy work on
the seven day thou shall rest and that
time and that that thy ox and thy ass
May rest and the son of thy hand made
and the stranger may be
refreshed and in all that's why that's
why the lord gave uh uh the the the
seventh day said it was made for a man
so man would have a rest period instead
of just working all the time seven days
a week he gave him six days of Labor and
seven day him and whatever his oxs and
whatever he plowed with or whatever M or
whatever he had get him a day to refresh
thems so they can recover from our
labor that's all I have to say lord gave
it to them as a day of
rest all right thank you for that hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our
next uh yes Jeron asked in 1st Samuel 28
verse3 is this the first
resurrection we know unclean spirits
know the truth example they give is acts
16 verse1 17 and Matthew 8 verse 29 so
again 1 samel 28 verse 13 is this the
first
resurrection all right brother Jerome
what' you say uh absolutely not it's not
the first resurrection um let's go read
those verses that you gave though T if
you can can you do the acts 16 and 177
first and then the Matthews
829 let's do those
first acts 16- 17 yeah and the same
follow Paul in us and cried saying these
men are the Servants of the most high
God which show unto us the way of
Salvation okay now let's go to to
Matthews 829
Matthew those two verses are the
examples they they gave about the the
angels and behold they cried out saying
what have we to do with thee Jesus thou
Son of God are Thou come hither to
torment us before the time okay now
let's go do the first Samuel now and
that's pretty much what the question is
really about the uh 1st Samuel 28 and3
M and the King said unto her be not
afraid for what sawest thou and the
woman said un I saw God's Ascend out of
the
earth so the Lord is not letting a
fallen angel and a witch raise Samuel
from the dead okay and again this is not
Samuel being raised in the first
resurrection
the first
resurrection takes place at the second
coming of the Lord okay which is beyond
us all right so let's go to Revelations
chapter 20 and read verse
4 Revelation 20 and verse
4 and I saw Thrones and they set upon
them and judgment was given unto them
and I saw the souls of them that were
beheaded for the witness of Jesus and
for the word of God and which had not
worship the Beast neither his image
neither have received his Mark upon
their forehead or in their hands and
they lived and reign with Christ a
thousand
years yeah so if the first resurrection
was during the time of of uh Saul when
he asked that witch to raise up Samuel
then Jesus should be here okay he should
be in Jerusalem right now and the wicked
shouldn't be running this earth right
now the righteous should be running the
Earth right now but we
know that ain't the time we in right now
because Jesus ain't came back yet
neither are the Saints running this
Earth that's right that's all I got on
it all right thank you for that as we
continue to move on to our next question
moving on so R FES ask are there any
restrictions to using bentonite clay
Indian healing clay in the bathtub to
remove toxins from your
system I haven't read anything in the
book where you can use the the bentonite
clay which is that Indian healing clay
also known as a det toxine clay but it's
supposed to treat some lesions and
ulcers and rashes and has uh also traces
of lead in it and it do have some side
effects so we say that you do your
homework do a full research and make
sure that it's okay for you to use but
uh always be careful whatever they
saying about some of this stuff and
that's all I got on
that and we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next yes cashian says what does 1 corini
15: 29 and 30 mean being baptized for
the
Dead all right why don't we go to that
First Corinthians
15 read that verse 29 and what does it
mean being baptized for the dead and the
guest caller shed some light from
there read 29 and
30 else what's shall they do which are
baptized for the dead if the dead rise
not at all why are they then baptized
for the dead and why stand we in
Jeopardy every
hour the reason that uh uh you
baptized it is to show that
uh death of Jesus and his resurrection
and we going to copy it let's go into uh
uh Romans the 6th chapter and we're
going to read a little bit we're going
to start reading at verse
one Romans 6 And1
yep what shall we say then shall we
continue in sin that Grace May
abound God forbid how shall we that are
dead to sin live any longer
therein but know ye not that so many of
of us as we're baptized into Jesus
Christ were're baptized to his
death he saying now how can we continue
in sin you know once we uh know the
truth he say so those that are baptized
in Jesus we was baptized into his death
just like uh uh when he when he uh like
going down in the water just like going
down into the Earth we were baptizing in
death go ahead and read therefore we are
buried with him by baptism into into
death that like as Christ was raised up
from the dead by the glory of the father
even so we also should walk in newness
of
life now that's what you tell you now
when you go into that water you're
supposed to go in as a a person that's
dead in sin but then when you come out
of that water you're supposed to be free
from sin and walk in newness of life in
other words stop breaking God's law go
ahead for if we have been planted
together in the likeness of his death we
should be also in the likeness of his
resurrection see what Happ he died he
went into the
ground and when he rose he rose out of
the ground just like you go in in in in
the uh uh uh ground in the water and you
get baptized as a spiritual dead person
when you come out you're just like a
spiritual living person just like Jesus
went in as a dead and come out living
what verse are we H that was in
five go ahead knowing this that our old
man is crucified with him that the body
of sin might be destroyed that hence
forth we should not serve
sin go ahead for he that is dead is free
from
sin now if we be dead with Christ we
believe that we also shall live with him
again knowing that
Christ so so that's that's what this is
talking about is being like Jesus
died for sin we died in our sin but
Jesus rose into eternal life then we
spoke we first when we come out the
water we going to rise as people that
are living for the Lord we have uh we
have uh left all our sins in the water
right no sinful person is dead now you
were raised as a god friend person
you're going to walk in newness of life
you're going to walk in the spirit at
the end just like and because of Jesus
rose from the dead that gave us hope
that if we walk in the spirit once we
got baptized we will also get him more
time let's go and look at First Peter
first chapter and read verse
three read it when he get
there blessed be the God and father of
our Lord Jesus Christ which according to
His abundant Mercy have begotten us
again into a lively Hope by the
resurrection of Jesus Christ from the
dead so now we in the same way when we
uh go down in that water we come up with
a lively hope that we going to live
forever Just Like Jesus when he went out
in the grave and come out he rose from
the dead that gave us a lively hope that
we will not only we have not only risen
from a spiritual dead that is the when
we left all our sins in the water but we
also going to be raised to a
physical uh uh uh uh from a physical
dead into eternal life just like Jesus
is so baptized until the dead is telling
you that hey when you go in that water
you going to go into the
center CER when you come out you're
going to be aive servant of God and if
you walk to Walk you're going to
eventually be
changed to God Immortal just like Jesus
is all I have to say yes sir looking
forward to that one
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next yes Victoria Smith says can you
explain St Luke 5: 36-
38 St Luke 536 through 38 brother Julius
share some light let's go there
t let's go to St Luke
5 and pick it up at verse
36 let's get the understanding of this
what do it
say and he spake also a parable unto
them now a parable is physical sayings
or physical allegoric sayings that point
toward spiritual
things and he spoke to the uh he spoke
to the uh Pharisees in Parables to
confound them because they were
self-righteous go
ahead no man put a peace a new garment
upon an old uhhuh if otherwise then both
the new maketh a rent uhhuh and the
peace that was taken not of the new AG
greth not with the old go ahead no man
put new wine into old bottle elsewh the
new wine will burst the bottles and be
spilled and the bottles Shall Perish now
he's talking to them in a parable but
he's really trying confounding them
because they're self-righteous pick go
go back up to verse 30 and look at this
Jesus is bringing a new way and bringing
in a New Covenant and uh bringing in
people into the word go ahead but the
Pharisees never liked them from the time
he uh started his ministry verse 30 go
ahead but their scribes and Pharisees
murmured against his disciples saying go
go
ahead why do you eat and drink with
publicans and sinners go ahead and Jesus
answered and said unto them they that
are need not a phys but they that are
sick because they sick and they need
help you judging them instead of helping
them go ahead at 32 I came not to call
the righteous but Sinners to repent
because the righteous is whole they
don't need it's the Sinners that need
recovering go ahead look at another
question they ask him go ahead and they
said unto him but why do the Disciples
of John fast often and make prayers and
likewise the Disciples of the Pharisees
but thine eat and drink so they judging
they judging Jesus said I came not to
call this uh the whole and the well and
the righteous I came to call Sinners so
he went on to a parable at verse 36 and
37 to show you I'm bringing the people
up under a New Covenant y'all want to
hold up up under the letter of the law
and judge and and everything and you are
hypocrites he called them blind Gods now
I'm bringing the truth and I'm
correcting y'all and y'all don't like
this so I'mma I'mma give y'all the
parable y'all trying to keep the people
up under the old I'm bringing up up on
the New Covenant I'm bringing a new way
of thinking I came that they might have
life and you trying to keep them up
under your ways you're blind God and
you're Hypocrites that's why he said uh
they murmured against them because they
never liked him and they showed you that
by setting them up lying on them and end
up crucifying him and he said because
you did this and you say you know your
sins remain upon you so this is a
parable showing you I'm bringing the
people up under the New Covenant and
taking from under you
Hypocrites that's all I got anybody want
to add to
that uh yes say it just said verse 38
yes
call in short to make it real short you
can't be on a New Covenant then turn
around and sacrifice the lamb for the
Passover that's yes sirant
okay thank you
right okay let's uh let's move on
then all right uh brother Harold would
like for you to explain first Peter 3
verse
19 okay let's go there tanzel and uh
brother Dre take it from there yes sir
let's go to read that that first Peter 3
and9 go ahead when you get it
brother by which also he went in Pre to
the spirits in
prison by which also he went and
preached to the spir bag of them read
Verse 18 go ahead but Christ also have
once suffered for sins and the just for
the unjust that he might bring us to God
being put to death in the flesh but
quickened in this by the spirit yes sir
go ahead by which also he went and
preached into the spirits in prison now
read verse
20 which sometimes were disobedient when
Once the long suffering of God waited in
the days of Noah while the ark was of
preparing wherein few that his eight
Souls were saved by water this is why
this is when he preached to the spirits
in prison it didn't say he preached to
man he said he preached to the spirit
in prison now let's go to first uh let's
go to uh second Peter the second
chapter second P Peter the 2 chapter and
and read verses four and
five go ahead for God spare not the
angels that sth but cast them down to
Hell and deliver them into chains of
Darkness to be reserved unto judgment so
now they in Chains of Darkness reserved
onto judgment we just read that in First
Peter the thir chapter Spirits in
Hebrews the first chapter verse 7 he
tells you he makes his angels Spirits
right that's what they are man is Spirit
man is flesh and blood right go ahead
brother go
ahead and spared not the old world but
save Noah the E person a preacher of
righteousness bringing in the flood upon
the world of the ungodly so that's what
we talking about here the same thing but
let's go to one last place let's go to
First Corinthians 15 and we gonna read
verse 44 because this is not talking
about man so somebody is telling you
that Christ went into the and talked to
the people in the graves no he said he
preached to the spirits that were in
prison now let's read verse 44 1
Corinthians 15 verse 44 go ahead it is
sown and natural body it is raised a
spiritual body there is a natural body
and there is a spiritual body so it is
sown in the grave a natural body and it
is not a spiritual body until it is
raised
it is raised the spiritual body go ahead
verse
45 and so it is written the first man
Adam was made a living soul and the last
Adam was made a quickening spirit and
that last Adam is Jesus and when he rose
from the grave he was made a quickening
spirit and if you read 51- 54 he tell
you a mystery there
right we going to be we going to be
Spirit beings at that time when PR but
not until then so that first Peter the
thir chapter verse 19 don't let nobody
tell you that is dealing with man that
is dealing with
angels during the times of Noah that's
all I got on
that all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question with the time check yes the
time is
811 by ran
Israel as in Zechariah 8 verse 19 what
are the fourth fifth and 10th month
Feast
mention all right Zechariah 8 and verse
19 when you get there brotherr they want
to know what are the fourth fifth and
10th month Feast mentioned here and the
guest caller take it from
there Zechariah
8:19 thus sayth the Lord of hosts the
fast of the fourth month and the fast of
the fifth and the fast of the seventh
and the fast of the 10th shall be to the
house of Judah joy and gladness and
cheerful Feast therefore love the truth
in
peace now read read it over again and
let's focus on one thing the word
fast read it over again thus sayth the
Lord of hosts the fast of the fourth
month and
the and the fast of the fifth what I'm
saying spell the word fast you
reading oh okay the fast of the fourth f
a s
now what I mean is how is it that a fast
can be a feast but keep
reading and the fast of the
fifth F A and the fast of the seven F
and the fast of the 10th
F shall be to the house of Judah joy and
gladness and cheerful Feast therefore
love the truth and peace
well you see first thing is those the
fast even though it's come under the
feast just like the weekly Sabbath day
come under the feast let's not the day
of Torment come under the feast those uh
uh uh the day of Torment is a fast so
now we don't keep these fast is because
the feast that the Lord told us to keep
is in Leviticus the 23rd
chapter and he said these are the feast
that you should keep
and the only day that he gave us a fast
was on the day of
atonement so what what month that that
come in that come in the seven
month that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move to our
next uh yes he also asked in numbers one
verse
45 numbers 14 verse 29
and Ezra 3 verse 8 can these scriptures
be used to show the age of
accountability age to uh age to be able
to be
baptized all right brother
Jerome what you
say brother tanzel let's go take a look
at those verses can you do numbers 14
and 29 first and then we'll do the Ezra
after that all right numbers 14 and
verse
29 your car shall fall in the wilderness
and all that were numbered of you
according to your whole number from 20
years old and upward which have murmured
against
me okay so when we at the Israel of God
through the word of God you know uh we
use this as a guide you know as far as
is when we
baptize okay uh and we use it as a an
example of age of
accountability okay now the other two
verses we going to go and read and see
if that same thing applies okay so let's
go to the uh Ezra 3 and verse
8 Ezra 3 and verse eight
yeah now in the second year of their
coming coming into the house of God at
Jerusalem in the second month began
jeruel the son of shtiel and Joshua the
son of josed and the remnant of their
Brethren the priests and the Levites and
all they that were come out of the
Captivity unto Jerusalem and appointed
the Levites from 20 years old and upward
and set forward the work of the house of
the
Lord okay now yeah you do see the um the
age of 20 years old and up with there
but this is a little different it's it's
talking about uh a a work that the Lord
wanted to set the Levites to do as far
as building the house the house of God
um skip down and read um well skip up
and read verse 6 and then skip down and
read verse 9 and 10 read verse
six from the first day of the seventh
month began they to offer burnt
offerings unto the Lord for the
foundation of the Temple of the Lord was
not yet laid Now read verse 9 and
10 then still jeshua the son of his
Brethren Cad cadel cadel and his sons
and the sons of Judah together to set
forward the workmen in the house of God
the son of hedad but their sons and
their brothers the Levites yeah and when
the builders laid the foundation of the
Temple of the Lord they said the pron
they app Peril with trumpets and the
Levites the sons of Asa with symbols to
praise the Lord after the ordinance of
David of
Israel okay and verse 12 can you please
verse 12 but many of the priests and
Levites and Chiefs of their fathers who
were ancient men for they had seen the
first house and when the foundation of
the house was laid before their rise he
wept with loud voice and many shouted
aloud for Joy yes so it ain't this it
ain't the same thing in that in that
numbers 29 when they rebelled against
God and God said you know he was going
to make them Wonder 40 years until all
those that from 20 years old and up was
going to die in that Wilderness within
those 40 years this this this is
different in this Ezra it's about them
building the Levites being to build the
house of God and he he gave a age right
there for 20 years old and up now let's
go to um to the numbers one and verse
45 numbers the first chapter
yeah we G pick it up at verse verse
45 and it reads so were all those that
were numbered of the children of Israel
by the house of their fathers from 20
years old and upward all that were able
to go forth to war in Israel okay so
kind of notice where it said all that
was able to go forth the war so that's a
little different too and I noticed from
verse 47 to 50 he not including the
Levites in this
number in this 20 years old and and up
so read verse 47-
50 but the Levites after the tribe of
their fathers were not numbered among
them for the Lord has spoken unto Moses
saying only Thou shalt not number the
tribe of Levi neither take the son of
them among the children of Israel yeah
for Thou shalt appoint the Levites over
the Tabernacle of testimony and over all
the vessels thereof and over all things
that belong to it they shall bear the
Tabernacle and all the vessel thereof
and they shall Minister unto it and
shall encamp round about
Tabernacle yeah so when it came to the
Levites regarding this this this uh it
says able to go forth the war that's a
little different than the accountability
thing too you know um so um when you tie
uh numbers the third uh the fourth
chapter it starts to break down the age
and it said from 30 years and up or 30
years to 50 when they was doing the work
in the Tabernacle and he named all three
of the uh sons of Levi and gave that
same
age from 30 years old to 50 and that was
the work that they were doing in the
Tabernacle it wasn't about the
accountability like the numbers the 14th
chapter verse 29 that we use as a guide
when we when we baptize okay that's all
I got
on right thank you for that Brothers we
continue to move on to our next question
yes moving on norless tapes as is it
possible that the tree of the knowledge
of Good and Evil back in the garden was
a literal fruit tree much like the tree
of the life with its 12 fruits on it
mentioned in Revelations 22 verses 1
through3 oh that's not possible but
brother Julius is going to further
expound on that question no it's
impossible that this tree is a literal
tree this is a spiritual tree let's go
to Genesis chapter 2 and show you who
this tree is and let's pay attention to
what we reading here Genesis
2 and pick it up at verse 8 and N kzel
Genesis 28 and9 go ahead and the Lord
God planted the garden e e and there he
put the man whom he had formed so we got
a physical Garden in Eden that God
planted go ahead and out of the ground
made the the Lord God to grow every tree
that is Pleasant to the sight and good
food now Pleasant to the sight and good
for food they came out of the ground
they grew out of the ground that the
Lord planted a garden in
now here's a different type of tree that
was not planted in the garden go ahead
and the tree of light also in the midst
of the garden and the tree of knowledge
of Good and Evil so now we got the tree
of life that was in the garden and we
have also the tree of knowledge of Good
and Evil trees don't talk this is phys
this is spiritual here Jesus is the tree
of life he told you that in John 3 and6
and he told you that in John 146 and
11:23 I came that you might have life
and have it more abundantly and another
time he called himself a branch that's
talking about Jesus now tree don't talk
skip down to verse 17 uh 16 and Look
What the Lord commanded the man go ahead
and the Lord God commanded the man
saying of every tree of the garden thou
mayest freely eat you could eat of
everything that grew out of the ground
you could eat of the tree of life which
is the spiritual tree which is Jesus but
go ahead but of the tree of the
knowledge of Good and Evil thou shall
not eat of it for in the day that thou
eatest thereof thou shall surely die
now let's go to Hosea 10 and show you
what they ate because if you read
Genesis chapter 3 the devil came and
said as God said that you should not eat
of every tree he said and the woman
quoted that and she said we can't eat of
the tree of knowledge evil L we die he
said You shall not surely die so we fast
forward to Hosea 10 and read verse 13
let's look at what they ate go ahead GF
plow the wickedness ye have reaped
iniquity ye have eaten the fruit of Lies
oh you have eaten of the fruit of Lies
trees don't talk they listen to the
doctrine of the devil and bought in
death so therefore you have because the
day you eat you shall surely die go
ahead because thou didst trust in thy
way and the multitude of thy mighty man
so you trusted the devil's word and
disobeyed God's word so therefore if you
have eaten God's word it would be no
death in the creation they listened to
the wrong one and brought in death so
this was this tree of the knowledge of
Good and Evil was none other than Satan
devil and if you want the rest of his
titles you can go to Revelation the 12th
chapter that old serpent he's a fallen
angel sisters and brothers one before
beings in the in the in the Garden of
Eden Adam Eve the Lord and Satan the
devil so they ate of the tree of the
knowledge good they listen to him and
bought in death let's go to revelation
22 you can read that on your own but
Revelation the 22nd chapter this tree
here is for the healing of the
Nations and pick it up at verse
one revelation 22 and verse one yes sir
and he showed me a pure River of Water
of Life clear as Crystal proceeding out
of the Throne of God and of the lamb
uhhuh in the midst of the street of it
and on either side of the river was
there the Tree of Life which bear 12 man
fruits and yielded her fruit every month
and the leaves of the tree were for the
healing of the Nations so this is a tree
here a little tree that's going you eat
a bit you could be healed that's all I
got anybody else want to add to that
think that's good brother thank you for
that as we move on to our next question
yes moving on Kenisha Mia asked for you
to explain Philippians 3 verse
9 all right let's go to Philippians
3 like to open this up to the
panel Philippians
3 and let's pick it up up at that verse
81 read 8 and nine and then we'll open
it up to the
patter yeah doubtless and I counted all
things but lost for the ex Excellency of
the knowledge of Christ Jesus my Lord
for whom I have suffered the loss of all
things and do count them but dumb that I
might Christ and found in him not having
my own righteousness which is of the law
but that which is through the faith of
Jes of Christ the righteousness which is
of god by
faith all right open to the P Paul here
was not leaning to his own understanding
he know that you have to have the Faith
of Christ the righteousness which is of
god by
faith he said I have suffered the loss
of all things yeah you definitely got to
have Jesus you got to have Jesus for
remission of sins so if you keeping the
Commandments and you reject Jesus and
you reject uh his
blood that'll cover your sin you going
to stand
before and he going to ask you about
them sins you
committed and his blood ain't covering
you know so you need that so you got to
have the blood of Jesus and you got to
keep the Commandments of God you got to
have the righteousness of Jesus and he
giving you righteousness through his
word and he giving you his righteousness
to cover your sins when you
repent okay so you got to have them both
you know anybody else want to ask them
they can and you will go through some
trials and some
tribulations and you gota strong and
have that Faith that's right don't let
your flesh leave always walk in the
spirit let's let's go 10 let's
me go
ahead people use this say you don't have
to keep the law all you have to do is is
uh uh being in the faith of Jesus I
think I got something that will solve
this real quick let's go into Romans the
chapter and we're going to read verse 28
then we're going to skip down and read
verse
31 Romans the 3
chapter and verse 28
first so therefore we conclude that a
man is justified by faith without the
Deeds of the
law okay so you justified by faith
without the Deeds of the law but if you
have faith but what does the law do
about faith faith do about the law skip
down and read verse
31 but do we then make void the law
through faith
God forbid yeah we establish the
law so now if you got faith in Jesus
Jesus told you that if you love him you
keep his Commandments which that's
that's right so now if you have faith
you don't make void the law you
establish the law how do you establish
by keeping it by
keeping yeah that's right yeah because
it if you got faith you got works also
that is right that is right and and
Abraham was called the father of Faith
that's right let's look go to Hebrews 10
and read verse 38 and
39 Hebrews 10 vers
389 now the just shall live by
faith but if any man draw back my soul
shall have no pleasure in him how you
going to draw back how you draw back
from
believing verse
26 but if we sin willfully after that we
have received the knowledge of the truth
there remaineth no more sacrifice for
sins that is how you draw back you draw
back by after you receive this
Grace then you willfully sin go against
the law of God that's how you draw back
and there remains no more sacrifice for
sin cor you want me goodidea draw back
bro not a good idea at all to draw
back
y all right hope that answered your
question we gonna keep moving I believe
we about 30 minutes left yeah so let's
move on uh Miss Wade asked for you to
explain 1 Corinthians 7
Verse
18 let's go to tanzel 1 Corinthians
7 read that verse
first about the circumcised and
uncircumcision all right go ahead
brother and the guest caller will weigh
in from
there is any man called being
circumcised let them not become
uncircumcised is any called in
uncircumcision let him not be
circumcised now what Paul is saying to
you if you find the Lord and you are not
circumcised don't get
circumcised and then if you find the
Lord and you're already circumcised
don't become
uncircumcised how can you become
uncircumcised find the force SC and Su
it back on no I'm not going to try and
explain what Paul is saying but I'm
going to tell you one thing Paul had a
an issue with the Gentiles being
circumcised now we going to see whose
word is bigger PA of the Lord let's go
quickly to Genesis the 17th
chapter and we going to read verse one
and two then we're going to skip
down 10 and 14 then going to give down
to 26 and
27 we're going to read quick CU I got a
couple of scriptures I want to deal with
on
this okay Genesis 17 pick it up at verse
10 uhuh 17 1 and
twoes 17 1 and
two Genesis 17 verse one and
two and when Abraham was 90 years old
and N the Lord appeared to Abram and
said unto him I am the almighty God walk
before me and be thou perfect and I will
make my Covenant between me and thee and
will multiply thee
exceedingly now skip down to verse 10
let's look at this
Covenant this is my Covenant which ye
shall keep between me and you and thy
seed after thee every man child among
you shall be
circumcised you shall circumcise the
Flesh of your foreskin and it shall be a
token of the COV betx me and
you and he that is o shall be
circumcised among you every man child in
your generation he that is born in the
house or bought with money or any
stranger which is not of thy
seed he that is born in thy house and he
that is bought with thy money must needs
be circumcised my Covenant shall be in
your flesh for an Everlasting Covenant
go ahead and the uncircumcised Manchild
who flesh of his foreskin is not
circumcised that Soul shall be cut off
from his people
he have broken
my that's clear because he's broken his
Covenant right right he's broke every
man child he shall it shall be cut off
because he's broken his C now this is
Abraham talking okay now let's go
quickly to Ezekiel the 43d chapter this
is when the Lord is going to come back
on this Earth Ezekiel 43 we're going to
read 1 through 7 real quick
eel
43 after he had brought me to the gate
even into the house that lookth towards
the east and behold the glory of the god
of Israel came from the way of the East
and his voice was like a noise of many
Waters and the Earth shine with his
glory and it was according to the
appearance of the vision which I saw
even according to the visions that I saw
when I came to destroy the city and the
Visions were like the visions that I saw
by the river chba and I felt upon my
face and the glory of the Lord came into
that go ahead and the glory of of the
Lord came into the house by the way of
the gate whose prospects is towards the
east so the spirit took me up and
brought me into the inner court and
behold the glory of the Lord filled the
house and I heard him speaking unto me
out of the house and the man stood by me
and he said unto me son of man the place
of my throne and the place of The Souls
of my feet where I will dwell in the
midst of the children of Israel forever
in my Holy Name shall the house of
Israel no more defile neither they nor
their kings by their whoredom nor by the
carcass of their kings in their high
places now that let you know that the
Lord is back on the earth isn't that
correct dwell in children of Israel
forever now let's that's after he came
through the East Gate came up out of the
Wilderness now let's go into Ezekiel 44
read verses one and two we're going to
skip then he brought me back the way of
the Gate of the outward Sanctuary which
lookth toward the East and it was shut
then said the Lord unto me this gate
shall be shut it shall not be open and
no man shall enter in it and buy it
because the Lord the god of Israel have
entered in by it therefore it shall
shut now that's now that's talking about
the Thousand Years of of Peace when the
Jesus going to be Ru ruling ruling this
Earth then I don't want because it going
to be man and Immortals on there he no
man comeing to this gate because the god
of Israel came through this gate
therefore that gate shall be shut skip
down and read verse
seven and that ye have brought unto My
Sanctuary
strangers uncircumcised in heart and
uncircumcised in flesh to be in My
Sanctuary to pollute it even my
house let's back up a little bit just
start just keep reading uh uh uh from
verse two just read
fast verse three and continue go
ahead it is for the prince the prince he
shall sit in it to eat bread before the
Lord he shall enter
he shall enter by the way of the porch
of that gate and shall go out by the way
of the same then brought he Me The Way
of the north gate before the house and I
looked and behold the glory of the Lord
filled the house of the Lord and I felt
upon my face and the Lord said unto me
Son of Man Mark well and behold with
thine eyes and hear with thy ears all
that I say unto thee concerning the
ordens of the house of the Lord and all
the laws thereof and Mark well the entry
in of the house and every going forth of
the
sanctuary and thou shalt say to the
Rebellion even to the house of Israel
thus sayth the Lord God oh ye House of
Israel let it suffice you of all your
Abominations that ye have brought into
My Sanctuary strangers uncircumcised in
heart and uncircumcised in flesh to be
in My Sanctuary to pollute it even my
house when you have offered up my bread
the f in the blood that they have broken
my Covenant because of all your
Abominations now that's what now now the
Lord called Israel he said suffice you
of all your
Abominations that you have brought
strangers into my house uncircumcised
and the heart and and uncircumcised In
the Flesh and you are the ones that caus
them to break my Covenant now skip down
and read verse
n thus sayith the Lord God No Stranger
uncircumcised in heart nor uncircumcised
in flesh shall enter into my sanctuary
of any stranger that is among the
children of
Israel now that's when the Lord is back
so through Gentiles are
strangers now let's go to two other
places right quick let's go in Exodus
the 12th
chapter and we're going to
read 43-
45 and then we're going to skip down to
48 when you get there and the Lord said
unto Moses and Aaron this is the
ordinance of the Passover there shall No
Stranger eat thereof but every
man get the Passover every year because
we the Passover represent Jesus but go
ahead say so no stranger e't thereof but
go ahead and read but every man servants
that is bought for money without has
circumcised him then shall he eat
thereof uhuh down
continue and when a stranger shall sourn
with thee and when keep the Passover to
the Lord that all his males be
circumcised and then let him come near
and keep it the shall be as one that is
born in the land for no uncircumcised
person shall eat
thereof one
law one law shall be to him that is
homeborn and unto the stranger that's a
journey for
m so now being that you have to be
circumcised to eat the
Passover and if you're not you cannot
partake of the Passover so now let's go
in the first Corinthians 5 and 7 and see
who the Passover
is read it when you get
there courage out therefore the old Le
that ye may be a new L as ye are
unle for even Christ Our Passover is
sacrifices for us so now if you want to
take
part in Jesus you have to be circumcised
because no uncircumcised person can take
part of Jesus because he's the Passover
right so now Paul said say if you find
yourself uncircumcised then don't get
circumcised didn't he say that yeah
let's see what Abraham did the father of
the faithful and that's it go back to
Genesis 17 and read verse 26 and
27 and the selfs same day was Abraham
circumcised and ishmail his son and all
the men of his house born in the house
and bought with money of the stranger
were circumcised with
them so now if
Abraham had stayed because the Lord came
upon him before he was circumcised ain't
that correct that's
right so then so if
Abraham listen to Paul uh uh uh then he
wouldn't have got circumcised wouldn't
he because this said if you found an
uncircumcision don't get
circumcised so then Abraham wouldn't
have got circumcised he said Lord I hear
you but I can't do that because uh I
found you in my
uncircumcision but no the same day that
the Lord told Abraham he sacrifice him
circumcised himself ishma and every male
in his
family so the scripture disagree with
what Paul said that's all I have to say
all right sister Deborah I believe we're
going into new
territory uh yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday September
the 4th
2024 jesson asks in Zechariah 5 verses
1-4 is this curse only part of the law
cuz it says cut off from the kingdom I
suppose
could you really elaborate on verse four
in particular the
consumption this in time
prophecy right Zechariah 5 verse one 10s
there when you get there go ahead and
the guest caller share some light from
there then I turned and lifted up my
eyes and looked and behold a flying rope
and he said unto me what seest thou and
I answered I see a flying Roe the length
thereof is 20 cubis and the bread
thereof 10 cubis then said he unto me
this is the curse that goeth forth over
the face of the whole earth everyone
that stealth shall be cut off as on this
side according to it and everyone that
sweareth shall be cut off as one that as
on that side according to it and I will
bring it forth said the Lord of hosts
and it shall enter into the house of the
thief and into the house of him that
swear falsely by my name it shall remain
of in the midst of his house and shall
consume it with the timber thereof and
the stones
thereof now all they saying is that
anybody that break his Commandments are
going to be destroyed if they don't
repent how many of them all of them any
any one of them if any one of them you
have broke them all let's go to James
the second chapter and read verse
10 for whosoever shall keep the whole
law and yet offended in one point is
guilty of
all that mean any one of the laws that
are hold 10 see people try and say
certain laws you don't have to keep you
have to keep them all so if you break
one you have broken you you have
offended in all of them
because the same God that said thou
shall not kill said Thou shalt not
commit adultery now let's go into first
John the third chapter and read verse
four 3 and four but we want to know what
sin
is whoever committeth sin transgress of
also the law for sin is a transgression
of the law so now any you break the law
you you are a sinner and sin is the
transgression of the law so if you
sin on purpose or intentionally let's
see what's going to happen to you let's
go into Hebrews the 10th chapter and
read verse 26 and
27 or if we sin willfully after that we
have received the knowledge of the truth
there remaineth nor more sacrifice for
sins but a certain fearful looking forth
judgment fire indignation which shall
Devour the
adversaries so that's not talking about
uh the end time prophecy let's talk
about alltime prophecy that's why the
she going to rest in the house of all of
all the people and tear it down that
breaks God's law no matter what the
generation is and if you sin willfully
you're going to get the ultimate
punishment the Lake of Fire that's all I
have to say all right hope that ansed
your question as we move on to our next
one moving on Valencia uh ask for you to
explain 1 Corinthians 4 verse 7 1
Corinthians 4 and 7 brother
Jerome let's go take a look at
it and you get it go ahead and
read who maketh thee to defer from
another and what H has thou that thou
did not receive now if thou did receive
it why doest thou glory and if thou had
not
receive he said why you going as though
you didn't receive it everything that
you have you received it from God
right uh let's go take a look at St
John chapter 3 verse
27 St John 3 verse 27
yeah wa John answered and said a man can
receive nothing except to be given him
from Heaven yeah that's all I got
on all right let's keep it moving
sister yes uh Ben F asks who is
bosra and also is the reference to Wine
related to practicing false Doctrine and
he gives Isaiah
63:
1-3 brother Dre what you say let's go
read that Isaiah
63 verses
1-3 no the the wine is not re related to
uh false
Doctrine but go ahead and read it when
you get it is related to
blood uh without uh 3 verse uh 1 23 one
to three okay who is this that comth
from Edom with th garment from
Bood that his glor is in his apparel
traveling in the greatness of his
strength I th speak in righteousness
mighty to save wherefore are thou read
in thy apparel and thy garments like him
that tread and the wine fat I have tried
the wine press alone and of the people
there was none with me for I will tread
them in my anger and trael them in my
Fury and their blood shall be sprinkled
upon my garments and I will stain all my
rainment this is talking about blood
here now let's go over to Isaiah
34 B up to Isaiah 34 and pick it up at
verse one when you get there go ahead
and read
it come near ye nations to hear and
hearken ye people that the Earth hear
and all that is therein the world and
all things that come forth of it for the
indignation of the Lord is upon All
Nations and his Fury upon all their
armies he have utterly destroyed them he
have delivered them to the slaughter get
down to verse
five for my sword shall be bathed in
heaven behold it shall come down upon
our Doom and upon the people of my curse
to judge me yes go ahead the sword of
the Lord is filled with blood it is made
fat with fatness and with the blood of
lambs and goats with the fat of the
kidney of Rams for the Lord have
sacrific in BO and a great Slaughter in
the land of adum so this bosra is a city
in adum where the live
is talking about the Lord dealing with
Edom in that time I hope that that
helps all right thank you for that
brother uh sister let's go to our next
question yeah uh Sanders Herring says in
Genesis 18 verse 19 how do you get this
from this verse now Sandra hering says I
know this is is written and these are
what he has written from a couple of
different scriptures and the first one
is If Abraham was your father you would
do the works of Abraham and then the
other scripture he given which is
paraphrase
says um and if
Abraham see
then are you Christ saved so
again uh he wants to know how do you get
this from Genesis 18 verse
19 um I don't know
exactly what he might be seeing in that
but let's go to that Genesis 18 and
verse
19 then we can open it up to the panel
and let's see and um Genesis 188
and pick it up at that verse 18 and
let's see what it's saying there brother
tanzel go ahead seeing that Abraham
shall surely become a great and mighty
nation and all the nations of the Earth
shall be blessed in him uhhuh all the
nations of the Earth shall be blessed in
him all the sons of Adam when they obey
and keeps God's Commandments go ahead
for I know him that he will command his
children and his household after him and
they shall keep the way of the Lord to
do justice and judgment that the Lord
may bring upon Abraham that which he ha
spoken of him and it was said that hey
Lord was like he know Abraham and he GNA
command his children and his household
after him and they shall keep the way of
the Lord that's why told Lord told us
teach our children and our children's
children but turn over to James 2 right
quick James 2
because you can have all the faith in
the world you got to have works too they
go hand in hand James 2 and 21 brother
go
ahead was that Abra Abraham my father
justified by works when he had offered
Isaac his son upon the
altar see thou have faith wroth with his
works and by works was Faith made
perfect so all so the faith and The
Works go hand in hand go ahead and the
scripture was fulfilled which said
Abraham believed in God and it was
imputed unto him for righteousness and
he was called the friend of God so we
see that Abraham believed God and same
for all his seed those that believe God
go get a good reward too read that next
verse and he was called the friend of
God go ahead you see then how that by
works a man is Justified and not by
faith alone so you have to have works as
well as faith and if you Abraham seed
you would do the works of Abraham
because he was a friend of God open to
the panel for anybody
else first thing is Abram was named
because from ABR to Abraham because God
made him the father of the faithful
that's right okay so anybody that
believe uh in God and keep his laws and
states he is a child of Abraham it have
nothing to do with a physical child it
is a spiritual child and also the Lord
told
Abraham in thy seed shall all the
nations of the earth be blessed right
right yep you become his seed and now if
you believe in in that seed then that
seed is Jesus let's go into Galatians
the 3 chapter
and we're going to start
reading at verse
26 for ye are all children all the
children of God by faith in Christ
Jesus for as many of you as have been
baptized into Christ have put on
Christ there was neither Jew nor Greek
there was neither Bond nor free there
there's neither male nor female for ye
are all one in Christ Jesus and if you
be Christ got nothing to do with a
physical child this is spiritual
children if you believe in Christ and
you've been baptized into Christ then
that
transgender race and color go ahead and
read then are ye Abraham see and Hees
according to the
promise do not if you be Christ then
your Abraham seed and a according to the
promise so now that seed that all the
nations going to be blessed in is Jesus
if you believe in Jesus and you walk in
his laws and statute then that makes you
Abraham seed his spiritual seed and all
the promises that God made to Abraham
you will be ass to them also that's all
I have to say all right hope that
answers your question as we move on to
our next one sister Deborah I believe we
coming down to our last question or two
but go ahead yeah uh he also says in
Acts 11 vers
11-8 it talks about Gentiles receiving
the word of God but verse 19 to end is
talking about the Jews he says
correct all right Jerome go
ahead that's a lot of verses
um I I can answer and say you correct
because from verse 11 through 18 those
verses are talking about the Gentiles
and then when you get to verse 19 let's
read that ver verse 19 it is talking
about the Jews so just read that verse
19 and we can move
on now they which were scattered abroad
upon the persecution that arose about
Stefan traveled as far as fenus and
Cyprus and Antioch preaching the word to
none but unto the only yeah so that
verse is talking about the Jews you know
the other verses talking about the
Gentiles that's all I got like we said
earlier this is whosoever will let them
come this is open for everybody that's
right yeah so all right
uh let's go to our next question sister
Deb yes yes
32 that's acts 11 yeah it was yeah it
was Acts 11 versus 11 through 18 so the
next question is 32 DBS asked can you
use
1611 King James with they say apocryph
but I don't know if they mean Apocrypha
so again can you use 1611 Kings James
with apoc Fe that's what they have all
right brother Julius I believe this is
going to be our last question of the
evening go right ahead if you want to be
entertained the definition of Apocrypha
means false and fake some people say
hidden it's false and it's fake who
authenticated it so now let's look at
what the books say two places real quick
tzel 1 John 4 1 John 4 and
one 1 John 4 and one let's look at just
one verse first John 4 and one when you
get it read it brother belov
believe not every Spirit but try the
spirits whether they are of God because
many false prophets are gone out into
the world so I did that I went and got
me an Apocrypha and I tried the spirits
I tried I read it and it was a joke to
me there's no salvation in it when I
read the this right here let's look at
what this book says Isaiah 8 and6 Isaiah
8 and16 the word bible means binding of
Books Okay binding of books now so what
did the Lord have have have uh have uh
his servants do and had King James had
King James translated go ahead and put
it in the
book verse 16 bind up the testimony seal
the law among my disciples so we got
there the Bible is the book of Law and
it's the book of testimony also prayer
bind the the testimony and seal the law
among my disciples none of that is in
the Apocrypha verse 20 brother to the
law and to the testimony if they speak
not according to this word it is because
there is no light in them so to the law
and the testimony the Old and New
Testament if they speak not according to
this word this right here then there is
no light in them sisters and brothers so
the Apocrypha to me is a joke and it's
got a whole lot of stuff in it and who
authenticated probably some random
scribes and some more people but who
authenticated it this right here is
written by these word are written by
holy men as God and they spoke as God
moved them by the Holy Ghost that's all
I
got that's correct brother Julius got
salvation I get salvation out of this
book
here these 66 books are enough to save
any man woman or child on the planet
that is right all right and uh this
other question you should be able to
answer this brother Cornell this is uh a
asking for information so we should go
to this one here this one will be the
last question which is daughter of Judah
asked in cities without a physical
church or other followers that does iog
have a way for young followers like
grandkids ages 16 through 25 years old
to connect with other Israelite youth
for the Bible studies online if there is
an online class how can my grandkids get
access to it and if not is there a way
through social media and then uh the
person says no I will post link to the
children's class and text lessons for
the Youth under this
comment okay um I'm not aware of any uh
class that we got online that you can go
to later I know they do
stream and um but that's all I got
unless somebody else got something on
that
but if anything changes other
than what I just spoke about we will
bring it to you but we ask that for now
you just join us every Saturday we will
be there and uh hopefully your kids will
be able to join us also but that's all I
got on
that all
right sister Deborah we have ran out of
time yes the time is 9:03
we want to thank everybody from all
around the world who sent in those
questions and who joined us this evening
want to say thank you if you submitted a
question we didn't get to it please
don't resubmit it sister Deborah will
take your question and she will add it
to the list and we will deal with that
question next Wednesday at the same time
but until we all come together again be
safe out there and may the Lord increase
our faith and strengthen us all close us
out brother tanay
Our Father which are in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
of our debts as we forgive our debtors
and lead us not into temptation but
Deliver Us from Evil thine is the
kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen amen